I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M GETTING MY NAILS DONE.
AND YOU SAID IT WAS
GOING TO BE FUN...
WHICH IT KIND OF IS.
ALSO, YOU SAID
THERE WERE GOING
TO BE OTHER GUYS HERE.
THERE ARE NO
OTHER GUYS HERE.
CHANDLER, THERE'S A GUY
RIGHT OVER THERE.
THAT'S A MAILMAN.
THAT'S OUR MAILMAN.
( mumbling ):
HI. HOW ARE YOU?
CHANDLER, DON'T WORRY.
THIS DOESN'T MAKE YOU
ANY LESS OF A GUY.
THAT DOES.
WHAT AM I SITTING ON?
I'D HATE TO THINK
WHAT THIS WOMAN WAS SCRATCHING
WHEN THIS BROKE OFF.
HEY, YOU KNOW
WHO USED TO HAVE
NAILS LIKE THAT?
NO.
Janice:
OH...
MY... GOD.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
JOEY, LET ME
ASK A QUESTION.
THIS HAS BEEN
DRIVING ME CRAZY.
WHAT DOES THIS LIGHT SWITCH DO?
OH, NOTHING.
DIDN'T IT DRIVE YOU CRAZY
NOT TO KNOW WHAT IT DID?
I KNOW WHAT IT DID--
NOTHING.
THEY WOULDN'T HAVE PUT IT THERE
IF IT DIDN'T DO SOMETHING.
HOW CAN YOU NOT CARE?
LIKE THIS.
HERE'S ANOTHER QUESTION
FOR YOU:
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
THAT LITTLE SILVER KNOB
ON THE TOILET DOES?
SURE. IT FLUSHES IT.
OKAY, GOOD.
NOW THAT YOU KNOW,
WHEN YOU COME OVER
WOULD YOU MIND
ACTUALLY USING IT?
HELLO.
HEY.
( yells )
( screams )
OH, MY GOD. WOW.
GUESS WHO WE RAN INTO TODAY.
JANICE.
IS THIS AMAZING?
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN?
WELL, UM...
I'M DIVORCED.
( gasps )
WOW.
YEAH, I'M RIDING
THE ALIMONY PONY.
( machine-gun-fire-
like laughter )
AND THERE IT IS.
I JUST CAME UP
TO SAY HI.
HI.
( laughing weakly )
AND YOU, SWEETIE,
I'LL SEE LATER.
OKAY.
I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT.
OKAY. BYE.
BYE.
BYE. BYE.
BYE. OH, BYE.
BYE-BYE.
BYE. BYE.
OH.
I CAN'T STAND THE WOMAN.
WHAT?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
CRAZY ABOUT HER.
I KNOW, BUT YOU KNOW
ALL THOSE LITTLE ANNOYING THINGS
THAT SHE DID
BEFORE WE FELL IN LOVE--
LIKE HER VOICE AND HER LAUGH
AND HER PERSONALITY?
THEY'RE ALL BACK
YOU KNOW.
AND SHE'S PICKED UP,
LIKE, NINE NEW ONES.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
BRINGING HER HERE?
THERE'S PEOPLE HERE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I'M TAKING CARE
OF IT TONIGHT.
YOU ARE NOT.
YOU HAVE NEVER BEEN ABLE
TO BREAK UP WITH HER.
WELL, I DON'T HAVE TO BREAK UP
WITH HER THIS TIME.
WE'RE NOT INVOLVED.
I'M GOING TO DO
A PREEMPTIVE STRIKE.
I'M GOING TO END IT WITH HER
BEFORE IT STARTS.
MY ASS IS, LIKE, FROZEN.
YEAH, TRY STICKING IT
IN THE FREEZER FOR 20 MINUTES.
I'M TELLING YOU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU REALLY WALK
ALONE HERE AT NIGHT.
I MEAN, YOU HEAR SUCH
STORIES ABOUT NEW YORK.
NO, IT'S REALLY
NOT THAT BAD.
I MEAN, I-I FOR ONE
FEEL PERFECTLY SAFE.
Men:
EM! EM!
( laughing )
HELP! HELP!
HELP!
COME HERE, LOVE.
NO-NO-NO, ROSS.
ROSS, THESE ARE FRIENDS OF MINE
FROM HOME.
LIAM, DEVON...
THIS IS ROSS.
OH.
HI, MATE.
HEY.
HOW ARE YOU, MATE?
HA!
THAT WAS A GOOD ONE, HUH?
"HELP! HELP!"
Emily:
SO, HOW ARE YOU?
I'VE BEEN MEANING TO RING
YOU EVER SINCE I ARRIVED
BUT, UM, WELL, I'VE
BEEN RATHER BUSY.
DO YOU REALIZE WE HAVE NOT SEEN
EACH OTHER SINCE THE NIGHT
OF THAT U2 CONCERT?
HUH.
OH, MY GOD, I THINK
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
THE LAST TIME
YOU AND I SAW EACH OTHER
WAS THE NEXT MORNING.
( chuckling ):
OH, LIAM.
HA! OH, LIAM.
SO, UH, WHAT, WERE YOU GUYS
PLAYING SOCCER OR SOME...?
( with fake British accent):
OR-OR SHOULD I CALL IT
FOOTBALL?
WE WERE PLAYING RUGBY.
WE'RE PLAYING A GAME
AT THE PARK TOMORROW.
YOU'RE WELCOME TO PLAY, TOO,
IF YOU WANT.
ROSS PLAY RUGBY?
I DON'T THINK SO.
( mirthless chuckle )
WHAT... WHAT'S SO FUNNY
ABOUT THAT?
WELL, I MEAN...
YOU'RE AMERICAN
TO START WITH.
YOU DON'T REALLY
HAVE RUGBY HERE.
WELL, WE DIDN'T
HAVE FREEDOM HERE
UNTIL 1776 EITHER, SO...
SO, GOOD, THEN.
WE'LL SEE YOU
AT RIVERSIDE
PARK AT 2:00.
CHEERS.
( grunting )
OH, BOY, I JUST
LOVE TO SING.
YES, I-I KNOW
THAT YOU DO.
I THINK ONE OF THE REASONS
PEOPLE WERE COMPLAINING
WAS BECAUSE
MOST OF THE PEOPLE HAD PAID
TO HEAR THE ACTOR
SING "OLD MAN RIVER."
OH, LOOK AT US.
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
THAT CUPID HAD A STATION
AT 14th STREET NAILS?
( machine-gun-fire-
like laughter )
OKAY, WE HAVE TO TALK.
I'M JUST GETTING OUT
OF A VERY SERIOUS RELATIONSHIP.
I KNOW...
AND I'M JUST GETTING
OUT OF A MARRIAGE.
I MEAN, TALK ABOUT
"MEANT TO BE."
RIGHT...
BUT I JUST THINK
THIS IS HAPPENING TOO SOON.
OH, TOO SOON,
TOO SCHMOON.
FACE IT, HONEY--
I AM NOT LETTING YOU
GET AWAY THIS TIME.
I HEAR YOU...
( chuckling )
BUT...
UNFORTUNATELY,
MY COMPANY...
IS TRANSFERRING
ME OVERSEAS.
OH, NO.
WHERE TO?
( gasping ):
TO PARIS?
NO.
NO, NOT-NOT PARIS.
TO LONDON?
OH, NO. ROME?
VIENNA?
OH, OOH, BARCELONA?
OKAY, COULD YOU JUST
STOP TALKING FOR A SECOND?
YEMEN.
( gasping )
THAT'S RIGHT, YES.
I'M BEING TRANSFERRED
TO YEMEN.
WHEN?
I DON'T KNOW EXACTLY...
OH.
WELL, I WILL
JUST HAVE TO SOAK UP
EVERY OUNCE OF CHANDLER BING
UNTIL THAT MOMENT COMES.
BUT I DO KNOW IT'S
SOMETIME TOMORROW.
DONE?
YEP.
HEY.
WHAT'S UP?
THIS SWITCH THING
HAS BEEN DRIVING ME CRAZY.
SO I TURNED IT OFF
AND CHECKED EVERY OUTLET.
FOUR DON'T WORK,
WHICH MEANS ONE OF THEM
HAS TO BE CONTROLLED
BY THE SWITCH.
SO, I PLUGGED
IN THINGS
IN ALL FOUR OUTLETS
THAT MAKE NOISE.
THAT WAY, WHEN I TURN IT ON
I JUST FOLLOW THE NOISE
AND FIND OUT
WHICH ONE IT IS.
I BET I STOPPED LISTENING
BEFORE YOU DID.
YOU KNOW, YOU-YOU ALSO COULD
HAVE USED, UH, LAMPS
AND THEN FOLLOWED THE LIGHT.
YEAH, WELL,
I'M USING NOISE.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT. SO,
EVERYBODY READY?
OKAY.
Monica:
HERE WE GO.
( low-pitched humming )
I HEAR SOMETHING.
WHERE IS IT?
( pitch rising )
( humming )
IT'S COMING FROM JOEY.
( humming continues )
OH, MY GOD,
THAT'S SO FREAKY.
TURN HIM OFF!
Sportscaster:
Goes back to England
with the set scrum
in center field
inside to Hall.
OOH, HEY.
Rachel:
HI.
CAN WE PUT ON THE NEWS?
I THINK
IT MIGHT BE RAINING.
NO. JUST HOLD
ON A SEC.
I'M WATCHING THIS
RUGBY THING ON ESPN.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE BIG DEAL IS.
I'M MAN ENOUGH TO
PLAY THIS SPORT.
DUDE, YOU'RE
NOT EVEN MAN ENOUGH
TO ORDER THE CHANNEL
THAT CARRIES THE SPORT.
HEY THERE, ROSS.
HEY.
JANICE.
( door closing )
YOU KNOW, UH...
YOU REALLY DIDN'T HAVE
TO HELP ME PACK.
WHEN YOU SAID ALL YOU WERE
GOING TO BE DOING BETWEEN NOW
AND THE TIME YOU LEAVE
IS PACKING
YOU REALLY DIDN'T LEAVE ME
MUCH CHOICE, DID YOU?
WELL, I THOUGHT I DID,
BUT I-I GUESS I DID NOT.
HEY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
OH, I'M PACKING.
YOU KNOW, I-I'M PACKING
'CAUSE I'M MOVING
TO YEMEN TOMORROW.
WELL, THANKS FOR TELLING ME.
I'M ONLY PRETEND
MOVING TO YEMEN, OKAY?
IT'S THE ONLY WAY I
CAN GET RID OF HER.
OH... GOOD ONE.
YEAH...
AND YEMEN.
THAT ACTUALLY SOUNDS
LIKE A REAL COUNTRY.
HEY, CHANDLER, COME ON.
I'LL SHOW YOU
HOW TO ROLL UP YOUR UNDERWEAR
AND STUFF IT IN YOUR SHOES.
IT'S A REAL SPACE SAVER.
YEAH, I KNOW. I DO THAT
'CAUSE IT MAKES ME LOOK TALLER.
Janice:
OKAY, CHANDLER.
COME ON.
OKAY.
JOEY, TRADE LIVES WITH ME.
NOPE.
MAN, LOOK AT THIS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU SAID
YOU'D PLAY RUGBY.
LOOK HOW BRUTAL
THIS IS.
HEY, I CAN HANDLE IT.
OH, PLEASE, ROSS.
YOU-YOU GOT HURT PLAYING
BADMINTON WITH MY DAD.
THAT'S 'CAUSE YOUR MOM'S DOG
KEPT-KEPT LOOKING AT ME.
OKAY, ROSS
LOOK-LOOK-LOOK-LOOK.
RIGHT HERE, IT'S
CALLED A SCRUM, OKAY?
IT'S KIND OF
LIKE A HUDDLE.
AND IS A HUM
KIND OF LIKE A SCRUDDLE?
( chuckling )
ROSS...
THEY'RE GOING
TO KILL YOU.
NOW, WHY ARE YOU
DOING THIS ANYWAY?
WELL, YOU SHOULD
HAVE SEEN THE GUY
THAT SHE USED
TO GO OUT WITH.
I MEAN, HE'S LIKE...
JOE RUGBY.
YOU'RE KIDDING...
AND HE PLAYS RUGBY?
THAT'S SO FUNNY.
( laughing )
OH, I SEE.
YOU DID THAT. ALL RIGHT.
( sighs )
ANYWAY, SHE THOUGHT
THE VERY IDEA OF ME
PLAYING RUGBY WITH HIM
WAS, LIKE, HILARIOUS.
SO, I'M GOING TO SHOW HER
HOW TOUGH I REALLY AM.
( snickering )
I'M SORRY. YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU ARE A TOUGH GUY.
YOU ARE THE TOUGHEST
PALEONTOLOGIST I KNOW.
ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
LOOK, ROSS COULD
TAKE CARE OF HIMSELF.
IT'S NOT LIKE
HE'S CHANDLER.
Chandler:
THANKS.
LOOK, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT ME, OKAY?
I'LL JUST LOOK
REAL ENERGETIC
AND STAY AWAY
FROM THE BALL.
I'LL BE THAT GUY
RIGHT OUTSIDE THE CIRCLE.
Ojomo to Back to Bracken.
OH!
OH, GEEZ.
OH. WELL, MAYBE
THERE WAS A DOG LOOKING AT HIM.
Joey:
OH, HEY,
ROSS, ROSS, ROSS.
YOU WANT TO STAY AWAY
FROM THAT GUY
AND THAT GUY
AND THAT ONE.
DUDE, THEY'RE
ALL HUGE.
THEY DON'T LOOK
ANY BIGGER THAN ME.
WELL, MAYBE THAT'S 'CAUSE
YOU'RE CLOSER TO YOU
SO YOU LOOK BIGGER TO
YOU FROM WHERE YOU ARE.
I'M JUST GOING TO GO
AND SAY "HELLO" TO
THE LADS, ALL RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
HI.
OH.
I KIND OF LIKED IT.
( whistle blows )
OKAY. I KNOW WHAT
I'VE GOT TO DO.
I'VE GOT TO GO "RED ROSS."
YOU KNOW, "RED ROSS"?
TOTALLY DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
COME ON, THE TIME THAT WE
WERE ALL WAITING IN LINE
FOR DANCES WITH WOLVES
AND THAT ONE GUY
CUT IN FRONT OF US
AND I-I JUST LOST IT?
HUH? SCREAMED AT HIM,
TURNED ALL RED?
"RED ROSS"!
NO.
YOU'LL SEE.
LIAM, DO ME A FAVOR.
YEAH?
TELL THE LADS
TO GO EASY ON ROSS.
IT'S HIS FIRST TIME.
YOU DON'T SAY.
THANK YOU.
OKAY.
GOOD LUCK, BABE.
Liam:
ROSS!
ROSS, COME ON!
GET IN HERE!
( players shouting )
Liam:
ROSS, COME ON.
( player growls )
COME ON...
ROSS!
ROSS, COME ON.
GET IN THE
BLOODY SCRUM.
Devon:
ROSS, GET IN!
( Ross yelling )
HELP! HELP!
HELP! HELP! HELP!
SOMEBODY!
OH! YOU... ARE... NOT
GOING TO BELIEVE IT.
JOSHUA CAME INTO WORK TODAY,
AND GUESS WHAT HAPPENED?
HE ASKED YOU OUT?
NO.
BUT I WAS SHOWING
HIM SOME CUFF LINKS
AND I FELT HIS PULSE.
SAUCY.
WHAT ARE THESE?
AH.
ELECTRICAL PLANS
FOR THE BUILDING.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
SHOULD I BE SCARED?
I KNOW THAT SWITCH HAS GOT
TO DO SOMETHING, OKAY?
SO-SO I WENT
DOWN TO CITY HALL
AND I GOT THESE.
ALL I HAD TO DO
IS PAY $25
AND WAIT IN LINE
FOR THREE HOURS.
WOW! IF ONLY MORE PEOPLE KNEW.
YOU KNOW, YOU REALLY DIDN'T
HAVE TO TAKE ME TO THE AIRPORT.
OH, PLEASE. EVERY
MOMENT IS PRECIOUS.
BESIDES, SOMEBODY HAD TO RIDE
IN THAT OTHER TAXI WITH
THE REST OF YOUR LUGGAGE
AND YOUR FRIENDS DON'T
SEEM TO CARE VERY MUCH
THAT YOU'RE LEAVING.
WELL, WE'RE NOT
REALLY THAT CLOSE.
OKAY, SO, I GUESS
THIS IS, UH...
YOU KNOW, GOOD-BYE, THEN.
OH, NO! NO,
IT'S NOT GOOD-BYE.
I'M NOT LEAVING UNTIL
YOU GET ON THAT PLANE.
OKAY, WELL, I GUESS
JUST WAIT HERE, THEN.
HI. I NEED A FAKE
TICKET TO YEMEN.
ONE TICKET TO YEMEN?
OH, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
I JUST NEED... I JUST
NEED A PRETEND TICKET.
I-I'M SORRY, SIR.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT WOULD YOU GIVE A KID
IF HE WANTED A TICKET
TO PLAY WITH?
ARE YOU TRAVELING
WITH A CHILD?
NO.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
SHE'S GOING TO THINK
THAT I'M HANDING
YOU A CREDIT CARD
BUT WHAT I'M
REALLY GOING TO DO
IS HAND YOU A LIBRARY CARD.
UH... SIR, A TICKET
TO YEMEN IS $2,100
AND WE DON'T TAKE
LIBRARY CARDS.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
( gasps )
DO YOU HAVE TO STAY?
AMERICAN EXPRESS?
ROSS!
OH!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY'RE DOING
THAT TO HIM.
I TOLD THEM TO
GO EASY ON HIM.
NO OFFENSE, BUT, YOU KNOW
SOMETIMES IT'S HARD
TO UNDERSTAND YOU
YOU KNOW,
WITH THE ACCENT, SO...
( blows whistle )
THAT'S JUST HALFTIME.
THERE'S MORE OF THIS.
Joey:
OH, HEY.
Phoebe:
HEY.
( panting ):
DID YOU SEE ME?
I WAS PRETTY GOOD, HUH?
THAT IS ONE FUN GAME.
RIGHT.
HEY, DO ME
A FAVOR.
COULD YOU JUST GRAB ME
A BOTTLE OF WATER? THANKS.
( gasps )
I-I THINK I'M DYING.
I-I REALLY DO.
OH, YOU POOR BABY...
TELL MY SON
THAT I LOVE HIM.
OKAY.
OH, EXCELLENT.
OH, OKAY, GOT TO
HAVE SOME MORE FUN.
ROSS, THEY ARE
KILLING YOU OUT THERE.
MM-MMM.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
SHE'S RIGHT.
YOU HAVE TO STOP.
WHAT? NO. NO,
I'M NOT STOPPING.
I'M "RED ROSS."
DUDE, YOU GO
BACK OUT THERE
YOU'RE GOING
TO BE DEAD ROSS.
I DON'T CARE.
I AM NOT QUITTING.
I AM GOING
TO FINISH THIS GAME.
IF YOU INSIST
ON DOING THIS
AT LEAST LET ME
HELP YOU.
NO. GOD, NO. THAT IS
NO PLACE FOR A WOMAN.
THOSE GUYS WILL
GRAB ANYTHING.
NO, THAT'S NOT
WHAT I WAS SAYING.
I JUST MIGHT KNOW
A FEW THINGS
THAT COULD HELP YOU
INFLICT SOME PAIN.
I LIKE THAT.
YEAH?
LISTEN CLOSELY:
DEVON HAS GOT A WEAK ANKLE.
HUH?
ONE SWIFT KICK,
AND HE'LL BACK OFF.
BAD ANKLE. GOT IT!
AND THAT BIG BLOKE
WITH THE BEARD...
UH-HUH?
HE'S GOT A TRICK HIP.
HUH-HA!
YEAH. AND DAVID
OVER THERE
I'VE HEARD THAT
HE DOESN'T WEAR A CUP.
WELL, I COULD USE THAT.
TRICK HIP, NO CUP.
OKAY, OKAY!
AND-AND LIAM--
LIAM'S GOT BAD KNEES.
YOU HIT HIM RIGHT
AND HE'LL GO DOWN
LIKE A LAMP.
BUT-BUT LIAM'S
ON MY TEAM.
I DON'T CARE.
YOU JUST GET THEM!
I'M GOING TO GET HIM!
OKAY, I AM GOING BACK IN.
( growling )
HEY, "RED ROSS," YEAH.
HI.
WHAT'RE-WHAT'RE, WHAT ARE THESE?
OH, JUST SOME PICTURES
I MADE AND HUNG UP.
THOUGHT THEY'D
BRIGHTEN UP THE PLACE.
THEY DO, DON'T YOU THINK?
( yipes )
NO, NO, DON'T! DON'T!
I KNOW THERE'S NO HOLE THERE.
I JUST REALLY LIKE THAT PICTURE.
OH, MY GOD, LOOK AT THIS!
OKAY, BUT THERE IS
A WIRE BACK THERE.
THAT SWITCH
IS CONNECTED TO SOMETHING.
I DON'T CARE. THE WIRES
HAVE COME LOOSE IN YOUR HEAD.
I-I JUST THOUGHT
IF I COULD FOLLOW THE WIRE
I COULD FIND OUT WHAT IT DID.
AND DID YOU?
NO.
DISAPPEARS BACK THERE
BEHIND THAT BASEBOARD.
FOR A MINUTE THERE
I THOUGHT IT WENT DOWNSTAIRS...
( gasps )
BUT IT DIDN'T.
SAY "HELLO"
TO MRS. KATRAKAS.
OH, MY GOD.
Mrs. Katrakas:
HELLO, DARLING.
HELLO, MRS. KATRAKAS.
NOW, ARE YOU SURE
YOU DON'T WANT
TO GO SEE A DOCTOR?
AW, NO.
THAT'LL JUST BRING ME DOWN.
THIS WAS GREAT.
I MEAN,
I-I-I WAS GREAT.
THIS WAS
A GREAT DAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M BUYING
EVERYONE COFFEE.
WOULD SOMEONE
JUST GRAB MY WALLET?
IT'S IN MY POCKET.
YEAH, SURE.
NO, NOT YOU.
LOOK, YOUR EYE'S
STILL POPPING OUT
A LITTLE THERE.
I'M GOING TO GO
GET SOME ICE.
OOH, ICE, YEAH.
I'M SO
IN THE MOOD FOR ICE.
YEAH.
AAH...
YOU WERE AMAZING
OUT THERE.
OH...
I KIND OF WAS, WASN'T I?
OH, MY GOD!
I MADE A MAN
TWICE MY SIZE CRY.
I MEAN, I HAVEN'T
DONE THAT SINCE I WAS FOUR
AND I WASHED MY DAD'S
PORSCHE WITH ROCKS.
YOU REALLY ENJOYED
YOURSELF, DIDN'T YOU?
PLEASE, ARE YOU KIDDING?
I-I HURT THREE HUGE MEN.
I GAVE A GUY
A BLOODY NOSE.
I MEAN, I'M-I'M
NOT PROUD OF IT, BUT...
I REALLY AM. I MEAN...
( chuckles )
AND IT'S ALL
BECAUSE OF YOU.
YEAH. WONDERFUL,
AMAZING YOU.
I THINK YOU'VE GOT
A CONCUSSION.
NO. NO, I'M SERIOUS.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
( squeals )
I'M SORRY.
DID THAT HURT YOU?
IT'S WORTH THE PAIN.
( chuckles )
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S NOT.
SORRY.
Announcer:
This is the final boarding call
for flight 664 to Yemen.
WELL, I GUESS
I GOT TO GO.
OH, MY BING-A-LING.
I'LL WAIT FOR YOU.
DO YOU EVEN KNOW
HOW LONG YOU'RE
GOING TO BE GONE?
WELL, JUST UNTIL
WE FIND AN ENERGY SOURCE
TO REPLACE FUEL.
OH. WELL, I'LL
WRITE YOU EVERY DAY.
OKAY.
15 YEMEN ROAD, YEMEN.
OKAY, GOOD-BYE.
GOOD-BYE.
CHANDLER?
NOPE.
CHANDLER!
JANICE, THERE YOU
ARE. THERE YOU ARE.
I HAD TO HAVE
ONE LAST KISS
AND ALSO, YOU SAID YOU
WERE GOING TO LEAVE
RIGHT AFTER I GOT
ON THE PLANE.
NO, NO. I-I WANT
TO SEE YOU TAKE OFF.
WELL, THEN I GUESS
I'M GOING TO YEMEN.
WHEN WE GET TO YEMEN
CAN I STAY WITH YOU?
ALL RIGHT. THE SUPER
COULDN'T FIGURE OUT WHAT IT DID.
THE $200-AN-HOUR ELECTRICIAN
I'VE HAD SEVEN
PRETTY SERIOUS SHOCKS.
I OFFICIALLY GIVE UP.
THANK GOD.
GUESS JOEY WAS RIGHT.
IT DOES NOTHING.
SEE?
I'M DOING IT.
I AM TOTALLY DOING IT.
I LOST IT.